[Music]
foreign
live stream it's Wednesday morning I'm
Nandita kimka and you're watching
morning trade with me well over the next
30 minutes we'll be talking about the
trade setup the stocks in news all the
earnings reactions that we are
witnessing ask you for earnings season
has kicked off and of course we're
getting we'll be getting all your stock
related queries answered by a technical
expert on the show so if you have any
queries send them into us on our live
feed and we will have them addressed but
before we do all that let's take a look
at the top headlines at this hour Wall
Street ends mixed as investors digest
big earnings Goldman Sachs reports a
weak set of numbers while streaming
giant Netflix delivers mixed results and
pushes back its Crackdown on password
sharing meanwhile hawkish Community from
fed officials signals more rate hikes
before a pause
Asian markets trade mixed with the
Nikkei edging lower in early trade sgx
Nifty is indicated for the Indian market
but with a negative bias
government-free imposes windfall tax on
crude oil setting it at 6400 rupees a
ton diesel exports will no longer invite
duty while the levees on patrol and jet
fuel continue to be nil
also on the show today brokerage is
turning bullish on big Pharma should you
look at buying now and stocks in the
spotlight are Tara coffee and icic
alombard among others
well let's get on board then our
technical expert for today shivangi
sarda of motilal financial services
joining in this morning good morning
shivangi good to have you on the show as
always you know the Nifty has been
consolidating after a nine day rally it
was the second day of losses yesterday
do you expect more consolidation to uh
kick in also the you know broad end of
the markets have been outperforming do
you expect the mid cap party to continue
good morning thank you for having me on
the show so you've seen that 15 has been
taking a pause after the nine days rally
and you know the good part is that even
on the declines day before yesterday we
saw that it's uh respected it's 50
exponential daily uh average on the uh
you know daily frame so somewhere or the
other supports are you know quite being
respected over here even yesterday we
saw that the previous day supports were
uh you know respected so somewhere the
indexes got stuck in a range of course
after a three weeks rally it is taking
some bit of a pause but then again the
overall Market if you talk about Bank ft
it is standing quite strong so Nifty is
uh you know not going to take a big uh
hit from these levels uh on the upside
we could see 17 777 as a hurdle uh which
did act as a hurdle in the last week
itself and then we could see support
near 17 500 levels now if we talk about
Bank Nifty we've seen that this index
has been resilient and is holding on uh
it has been making higher lows from the
last five sessions and despite Nifty
being weak this uh index is holding
because of the heavyweights private uh
space which is uh you know performing
quite well so uh uh Bank Nifty I would
suggest Buy on decline strategy to
continue in this index with the Target
near 42 750 levels and a support near 42
000 zones
right so those are the levels to watch
out for on the Nifty and Bank Nifty
shivangi how would you be trading SBI in
the next couple of sessions given the
fact that the board in fact has approved
a two billion dollar fundraise via
long-term debt uh so what are the kind
of levels you'll be watching out for SBI
and how should one treat that counter
Tailwind from there uh specifically SBI
has been performing from the last four
months and we've seen good amount of you
know loans being built up with good
volumes in the last two sessions and
it's come out of its daily range it's uh
trading above its key experiential
moving average on daily Frameworks as
well and uh you know somewhere on the
other it is holding uh even yesterday we
saw it held on to its cater Tire zones
so uh definitely the stock is going to
be positive for the next few sessions
and we could expect 565 levels over here
uh 535 would be important support to
watch out for
right uh you know shivangi hold that
thought we'll come back to you and
discuss specific stocks stocks stock of
the day brokerage call of the day all
those things in a bit but let me also
bring on board the anubhav sahu of money
Control Pro uh you know we'll be talking
about the Pharma pack you know this uh
index has been outperforming the Nifty
of the last one month and we've seen
Nifty Pharma index gain somewhere around
eight percent in the last one month and
it has outperformed the Nifty by
somewhere around 300 basis points or
their bouts uh one of good morning good
to have you on the show a lot of these
uh brokerages are turning bullish on
some of these uh big Pharma names like
sun Pharma shipla what is the Outlook
looking forward on these companies going
forward
your point that uh you know the farmer
started out performing and there's a
good case for that uh because of the
macro uncertainty and also the fact that
Pharma in general has underperformed
significantly in last week in 20 months
uh now coming to your specific point
yeah I'm
because of the specialty portfolio which
is focused on Derma and Ophthalmology uh
however what we are looking forward to
as far as the uh the common quarterly
result and uh you know the commentary
form management is about the clinical
trials uh from the flagship product
Illumina because in past they have been
having some difficulty in getting that
done
uh secondly for sun Pharma in particular
we would be also uh looking forward to
you know the full ramification of
ransomware uh item page which happened a
couple of months back and so on that
front so as far as obvious constant we
are uh uh kind of a neutral or equal
weight on sun Pharma partly because of
valuation which is on the higher side
uh similarly for cipla I think that they
are what they are trying to replicate
they are trying to replicate the success
of respiratory portfolio into a new set
of products in the peptide area uh here
again the near-term concern is the delay
in launch of adware uh which has been
impacted because so U.S MTA uh
observation for the indoor plant uh here
again we are uh on the sideline just
simply because evaluation but in the
last farmer space we do have some
preferences uh like for example we do
like Dr Reddy's uh because of the reason
they are doing on The Chronic portfolio
side as for India is concerned and they
are having some good traction as for the
Emerging Market Portola Wisconsin uh
zyrus life is also interesting for an
evolution perspective as well as the
attraction by singers and uh we are also
positive on ifta Labs we think this is
infant valuation compression and they
are seeing some kind of adaptation on
the uh you know the API capacity as well
as the starting API side
we are in the thick of earning season
we've seen IIT disappoint when it comes
to earnings you know both Infosys and
TCS have handed in a very disappointing
set of numbers but what about Pharma can
we expect any kind of a positive
surprise where Pharma earnings are
concerned this time okay yeah so as far
as the top line is concerned with Pharma
we expect uh to be a steady quarter uh
chiefly led by uh U.S attraction uh
because of the recent launches for
example that of a rev limit and that can
have a positive uh cover for companies
like Dr Reddy's tattoo uh
uh on the India front of the ongoing flu
season will have some incremental uh
positive impact uh but on the margin
front we think that the pressure would
continue uh uh for both the geographies
I think for the us so we continue to see
that uh the pricing erosion will remain
in the range of a higher single digit to
low double it is it uh and because of
the normalization of supply chain I
think the new supplies have come up also
even though in some pocket they are some
uh shortages but I think pricing erosion
in near term will continue like this uh
similarly for India I think the
operating environment is again back to
people with times so which in turn means
a similar level of travel expenses
similar expenses as for them are
enforcement Mr enrollment discussion and
so so on the market front we don't think
too much of a relief for Pharma sector
but if you're talking about earning
surprise there could be other segments
of the healthcare which can see positive
tractions sequentially
and I think uh the sector the segments
would be to be watched in that case
would be that of Diagnostics uh wherein
it looks like your pricing uh uh drag
which we have seen for last few quarters
probably May and may be abating a bit uh
similar for apis I think uh you know a
single part of Industry inventory D
stocking has happened and uh and some of
the companies May report start report
you know benefit of a lower raw material
prices
write any other risks that you are
spotting when it comes to Pharma names
going forward because pricing erosion uh
you know some bit of pain would persist
for some time as you mentioned but what
about regulatory issues do you see some
kind of a relief when it comes on that
front
uh I think I think it would remain a
mixed back for Indian Pharma as we have
seen the last one year as well I mean
the likes of surplus and Pharma uh you
know Glenmark they had adverse
observation and I think a similar kind
of work things can I mean and then we
cannot I mean those kind of expectation
can still be there I mean but at the
same time uh uh you know the regulatory
inspection is a part and parcel of this
sector wherein which also helps to you
know for new launches
uh other thing as well as I mentioned
for Indian Pharma domestic farmer is
concerned the operating environment is
back to Big covet time so I think the uh
the increase in operating HMS is
something to be watched
as far as
right you know we spoke about all the
large cap Pharma names but any uh Pharma
companies in the mid cap space that you
are finding attractive at the current
juncture
all right so in terms of difference uh
uh you know among the sub segment we
continue to like the CDM of space uh we
have seen a prefer picked Sinjin in fact
which has had a significant time
correction and recently has started
paying out uh I think Laura's lab is one
stock in the CDM of space and synthesis
space which one is to track wherein they
have been a significant valuation
compression and I think is uh street is
overly concerned about the
opportunity uh secondly on the API side
I think the basically went positive on
this company which is the sole
manufacturer of vitamin D3 API fermented
by attack uh I think uh uh the valuation
is discounting the uh the challenges in
their portfolio uh at the same time they
also overhang as well as you know the
leverage this consent and they are
taking steps from that direction I think
that would be positive uh other than
that I think the uh I think selectively
uh you know uh one should be looking for
opportunities in apis and diagnostic
space
yeah right well those are the stocks to
watch out for in the Pharma space with
that number of thanks a lot for taking
out time this morning and joining us and
sharing your thoughts with us let's go
back to shivangi then and talk about
some stock specific action uh you know
stock of the day according to me is Tata
coffee it reported a pat growth of
somewhere around 20 on a wire basis and
revenues also have come in double digits
on the back of hot demand if you look at
the stock it has come off its 52-week
lows but still quite a you know quite a
way to go when it comes to a 52-week
high uh any kind of action You're
Expecting in this talk in today's
session or the next few sessions going
forward
so looking at Tata coffee this stock has
been beaten down for you know quite a
lot of uh quite a long time and uh we
see that Weekly frame it is uh trying to
you know recover from its uh you know
lows but then again there has been uh
loss of momentum in this top even when
we saw that the stock had rallied for
four sessions
so I expected the movement here is going
to be quite uh capped on the upside
however one could see that the stock
could move in the range between 212 to
205 levels
right so those are levels to watch out
for on Tata coffee here from coffee
let's move to Spirits then you know uh
the hot brokerage call of the day for me
is United uh Spirits Macquarie has in
fact come out with a underperformed
rating on this talk and has packed the
target at 650 rupees a share now you
know there could be a spirit War uh so
to say brewing in Delhi because uh you
know the fact that New Delhi has refused
to renew a purno records records the
license uh will turn out to be a
positive for United Spirits however
Macquarie believes that this positive
will take some time to reflect and it
believes that there is limited room to
cut costs when United Spirits is
concerned the Target price is you know
over 100 rupee lower than uh what the
current price is for United Spirits uh
do you also expect this company this
stock to you know head southwards from
here
uh looking at uh you know the chart
structure the stock has been uh you know
trading in a range but then again on
week uh on daily frame it has not uh
surpassed it's the key moving average so
uh somewhere or the other we've seen
Court run up in the last two days but
then it has to hold above 775 levels for
an up move towards uh you know good uh
800 levels so a hold from these levels
would take the stock towards 800 with
the stock near 760 zones
right uh that's the call on United
Spirits uh let's take up a query then uh
on mind LTI Mind Tree this one is coming
in from uh Prabhu and he wants to know
whether it's the right time to average
it of course we've seen uh mid cap I.T
also come under Fair bit of pressure
after you know the earnings picture that
in fact after the kind of weak earnings
that was handed in by Infosys and TCS uh
would you advise the investors to
actually look at these this kind of
depth that we saw on some of these mid
cap counters it counters to you know buy
into these right now on dips
so looking at you know the entire ID
space the stock has you know tried to
recover but then again with some sort of
buying we can see that again the uh the
stocks the index is not being able to
hold at higher zones and then it is
tackling down again so clearly the
strength is missing over here and I feel
that you know uh there has been a uh you
know quite a lot of volatility in the
last three days and the stocks have all
uh you know uh sort of uh near its key
support zones but I feel that there is
uh you know uh there might not be any
more pain in the stocks but then again
uh the stocks to deliver return will
take time because of the loss and
movement
we should stay away yeah right stay away
from uh some of these mid cap I.T names
right now uh let's talk about another uh
company that came out with this results
yesterday ICICI Lombard the fourth
quarter profits have jumped 40 percent
and the net premium earned has also come
in in double digits around 12 or so on a
YY basis some of the brokerages have
come out with Target cuts on this
counter they've said that this is a
mixed set of numbers how would you
advise investors to play this now going
forward
uh definitely so looking at uh you know
I see iclomb but we've seen that uh this
entire uh space has uh you know uh sort
of bottomed out and even with icslr
we've seen that there has been good
support uh taking their thousand levels
so uh after which the stock is moving
quite well from the last one week so the
stock is definitely uh you know gaining
some momentum on monthly frame it has
seen a negation of the lower uh highest
lower lows as well so uh somewhere we
could expect uh you know good returns
over here and we could immediately
expect 11.75 here with a support near
1105 levels
right uh you know I also want to get in
your thoughts on some of these oil and
gas names like ongc or in India and of
course Reliance Industries because uh
Reliance will be reporting numbers on
Friday but you know there is news flow
that the government has reimposed
windfall tax again uh windfall gains tax
on on crude output and it has been set
at 6400 rupees a ton uh you know bad
news for some of these companies like on
GC and oil India and how how should one
play Reliance ahead of the earnings
uh absolutely so looking at uh Reliance
this stock has uh you know uh taken a
hit in the last two days and uh weekly
we've seen that whatever gains it so it
has now you know tanked out even uh you
know if we see the broader picture
Reliance has not truly moved from the
last three months it is hovering in a
very uh narrow range and uh we uh could
see a bit of a pause if the index uh and
uh you know the effects on the reliance
as well so I would recommend that we
could wait and watch in Reliance and
once it holds 2350 levels we could then
uh you know shift to a bias over here
now talking about ongc specifically this
stock is looking quite good uh it is
coming out of its uh you know weekly
weekly schedules of 160 levels and uh
the stock is placed quite positively
because it is holding well on its daily
frame now uh this stock could see an
side towards 166 zones with a stop near
155.
right OMG is looking good on charts I
know we discussed insurance but I want
to also get in a query addressed for
aniket Kumar he wants to know your
long-term thoughts on LIC for the next
two to three years uh you know on a YTD
basis this talk has shaved off over 20
just coming off its 52-week lows uh
would you advise someone to look at it
right now or is it time to stay away
from some of these Insurance names
uh Insurance teams if we talk about uh
you know LIC in particular this stock
has a non-feeded momentum from the uh
you know last three months in fact this
talk is uh you know making lower highest
lower lows at any bounces so uh I I
would suggest we could stay away from
this talk in particular not the entire
sector
right stay away from LIC but not the
insurance sector per se uh the next
query is coming in on punawala fincorp
and Ankit chavan has written in you know
this talk has seen a good gains over the
last seven days or so there was a block
deal in the counter and stock has doing
has been doing pretty well uh how are
the charts looking for it over the next
two to three months now
uh this chart is looking amazing and
we've seen that you know the monthly
frame it has just come out of its
Consolidated phase and we could see that
this stock is consistently performed
from the last three years and it has
continued to do so at all at higher
levels so definitely uh it is a very
strong counter and in fact right now it
is kind of making a you know headed
shoulder pattern on daily frame and the
breakout can be seen as well so we could
expect good levels over here in fact and
this was uh you know on my radar as well
so definitely we could see 320 and then
325 levels over here with a stop near
300 300.
right uh let's take up the Dex query
then this is coming in from Bikram munmu
and he has a query on IRCTC uh you know
over the last five days you've seen a
decent gain of three percent or
thereabouts but on a YTD basis of course
the stock has hasn't done all that well
uh would you uh advise investors to look
at it for the short term or is it time
to stay away from some of these rail
counters as they have come off their
highs that we saw last year
uh yes so absolutely there has been a
lot of momentum in the railway uh you
know counters and we've seen that IRCTC
specifically has you know taken support
near 560 uh five levels uh and it is now
you know trying to uh you know gain
momentum but then again there is uh it
is trading in a you know falling uh
trend line or daily frame so once it uh
you know breaks that channel and only
then we will see a good uh you know run
over here on the contrary rpnl uh is one
stop which is looking quite good over
here and we could expect good uh returns
because this the stock is held on to its
uh you know higher zones and we could
expect immediately 78 levels over here
with a stock near 74. so these these
stocks can be looked out for this space
right uh moving on to some of these Auto
ancillary companies uh jifin has written
in and he has a query on exide uh this
stock is moving towards a 52-week highs
good time to look at it and also we have
a query on Apollo tires uh this one is
coming in from yagnesh and he wants to
know your short term as as well as your
long-term targets for Apollo tires so
how would you advise investors to look
at these two counters now
so looking at excite uh you know this
stock has uh been uh stuck in this same
rate from the last five months in fact
it has not surpassed it's uh five months
high of 194 and uh you know leader has
it broken 170 levels so uh we could see
some sort of a consolidation which is
going to be expected to continue over
here once it uh you know surpasses uh
195 levels only then we could see a good
uh you know breakout in a momentum over
here now uh looking at uh I'm sorry what
was the second stock Apollo tires
shivangi the second stock is Apollo
tires
okay so looking at a polo tires uh you
know this stock is in fact given a good
price volume surge in a previous session
and we've seen that the stock has uh you
know given uh the the base of the stock
is gradually shifted higher from the
last three weeks so definitely this
stock is better placed and uh quite uh
you know the risk reward ratio wise also
the stock is looking quite positive for
an up move near 345 levels and a stop
near 325.
right uh shivangi what's your call on
Tata chemicals this talk you know
slumped somewhere around six percent in
yesterday's session the company has
slashed suda Ash prices and we have a
query coming in from Tariq Ahmed who
wants to know what to do with this talk
at this juncture should one buy it use
this dip to buy into this
so uh Tata Capital we've seen that you
know it has given up all its gains of
the last three to four weeks and we've
seen that there has been a sharp
downtake in the last two sessions so uh
definitely uh news flows uh have you
know made the stock week but then again
it is broken in support of 9 30 levels
uh you know
so that
stock is going to see a little more pain
over here if not an upside but that we
could expect 900 levels over here and uh
950 would be an important resistance
levels to watch out for this talk right
shivangi is about time for one last
query this one is on Cesc uh this stock
has been in a steady downtrend and over
the uh like you know over the course of
this year on a YTD basis it has lost in
double digit somewhere around 12 percent
or so more downside
so uh you know looking at this talk in
fact even in the previous year we've
seen that the stock has uh not performed
and uh saw a downside and uh even uh
right now from the last uh you know many
months uh it it is not been able to you
know move uh above its resistance levels
so the the resistances are casually also
shifting lower so some sort of a pain or
should be seen over here but then again
uh the momentum is quite low over here
so I would recommend we can wait and
watch but no action in the stock
right wait and watch where CSC is
concerned well with that I think this
wraps up our query segment for today but
before I let you go shivangi share your
stock recommendations for the day for
viewers
yes so uh my stock recommendation would
be uh first is igl we've seen that there
has been a good you know run up over
here and from the last three weeks we've
seen that the stock has been
consistently performing and making
higher highs higher lows over here stock
is quite positive with a you know good
amount of a long built up over here on
the open interest Edition so uh
expecting a target of around 505 with a
stock near 485 zones uh now my second
pick would be on Chola Finance you've
seen that this stock also coming from
the entire uh you know sector and space
uh quite a lot of positive action it has
given a Poland flag patent uh you know
breakout uh on daily frame and holding
quite well and we could expect good
amount of levels over here uh which uh
the stock is expected to move around 875
levels with a stock near 820 source
right so those are the stock
recommendations from shivangi with that
shivangi thanks a lot for taking out
time joining us this morning and
addressing all our viewer queries well
with that we are completely timed out on
this edition of morning trade it's a
good buy from me and the team that put
the show together but stay tuned to
moneycontrol because coming up next is
opening bell
[Music]
thank you